{
    "id": "fdad999f8afa46e2a9a99b721b658298",
    "title": "At, On And In",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We will come and see you …………………. Christmas day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a9fc4a1c526f4051878cb3be4433fbc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "It happened ……………….. the week before Christmas.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85fce2d4d0214e67af72b8ea6d5f1c73"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen him …………………… years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d65245d6f40f42dc84d00eed1808e6c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to see him ………………… lunchtime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "630bffaded774fd9a146e41cbe9cdf0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I first met her ………………….. a rainy morning in June.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3ddf46f60fa6402e9b8d50914c26acdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stanford is ……………………… the river Avon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7dfa5cbc0a04a0b951fc0f4953d9fda"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t many apples ……………………… the tree this year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a478d334ec1548f286eb427a86c54f2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the good-looking girl ………………….. the sixth row?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18c65a7c500f422280f492abd2c0e69c"
        },
        {
            "question": "As there was no room …………………… the bus we got off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7caf8714ebfa442183f06cc39714a45e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is always ……………………… the hairdresser’s.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cdc6ea0015734fc78363e00cdc046f46"
        }
    ]
}